So by now we've all heard of Florida's Governor George DeSatan and his decision to block an AP
advanced placement black history course saying that it lacks educational value. People are
outraged as they should be. Many of us thankfully understand this is a part of this continuing
agenda to invoke white supremacy into the educational system by a myriad of methods.
I saw this comment and it really gave me pause probably because it's not what most of us think
it is. The course includes black queer theory and prison abolition. Those are the parts they
sneak in to indoctrinate. Tell the whole truth not half. This is about their agenda on kids.
Who's there? Y'all keep trying to push this whole idea of a gay agenda when the reality is these kids
who turn out to be gay adults are coming from many times homes. Furthermore he's saying that it also
includes prison abolition and that that is something that is sneaked in, snuck in, snaked in. Baby
regardless of whether you disagree with these things or not there are still black people that
are a part of the queer community and there are of course black people a part of the prison
industrial crisis. Why would these topics which by the way are simply topics that are a part of a
other topic they're not even full-on courses within the course. Why would they not be included?
Why if they are included does it indicate that this would no longer be an educationally
substantive course if so? Listen close. It is physical and mental exploration that's expanded
this world and brought so many riches to colonizers. Rejecting of this course is just another example
of them continuing to impede black folks from doing the same.